you have an iconic scalp you have an
iconic head jacob thank you so let's see
if you can id these other gentlemen just
from their heads damn it okay oh that's
mike tyson that's way too easy you can
see the face tattoo okay we started out
sorry i'm getting too ahead of myself
yeah you are
next one
terry crews not even close oh what
[Laughter]
can you see what's going on
what the what's happening there man
i'm definitely not going to get who that
is someone you've probably shared the
screen with i've worked with someone
bald
know a guy by the name of
nick fury sam jones awesome
oh my goodness i love you sam i'm so
sorry i even realized what do you got
okay that's the be vin diesel
oh my god it's like the complete
opposite
is like yes
next week
okay that has to be vin diesel there it
is oh finally family finish strong
family
oh that's me